youproxytube.com 2015-03-20

# Privacy Policy - Unblock YouTube | Free YouTube Proxy

## Privacy Policy

Our service may collect information about you during your visit. This document describes the information we collect and how it is used. 

**Server Access Logs**

Our server logs all requests. The data recorded includes information provided by your browser (user agent and referring page) as well as the requested URI, the time and date and your IP address. The data recorded in these logs may be used for detecting and preventing abuse. We may also collate this data for statistical purposes. 

**Service Logs**

The service provided on this website allows access to external, third-party websites. We may record your IP address and the websites you visit. The logs are used primarily for monitoring requests and ensuring no illegal activity is undertaken. Any violations of our terms of use may result in disclosure of the data recorded in our logs to an appropriate third party, which may include your Internet Service Provider (ISP) or local authorities. We may also be required, by law, to provide logs of our service and if requested, such data will be disclosed. We may also use service logs for stastical purposes. 

**Cookies**

Our website stores a cookie on your computer, if allowed by your browser's privacy settings *. The cookie used by our service uniquely identifies you to the server and allows our website to remember your preferences. 

We may also use third-party advertising partners on our website. Advertisers may send you cookies or use web beacons. We have no control over cookies, web beacons or the information collected by our advertisers. Consult the third-party advertiser's privacy policy for more information on their practices. 

How are we handling cookies? 

The service we provide allows indirect browsing of third-party websites. A third-party website may attempt to send cookies to the user. We store these cookies on our server and automatically forward them onto the target server. Your cookie data is treated strictly confidentially, stored privately and deleted soon after you leave our website. If you would prefer us not to store your cookies, please disable the "Allow Cookies" option. 

The service we provide may attempt to forward third-party cookies from the websites you choose to browse. We have no control over indirect cookies and you are advised to consult the privacy policy of the applicable third-party website. If you do not wish to receive any such indirect cookies, please disable the "Allow Cookies" option. 

* For more information on configuring your browser, see [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1) or the documentation for your browser. We are not responsible for the content of any third-party websites. 

**Advertising Privacy Policy for youproxytube.com**

The privacy of our visitors to youproxytube.com is important to us. 

At youproxytube.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit youproxytube.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. 

We also use third party advertisements on youproxytube.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
